‪THE LOVE LAB
‪On this final night,
‪we will now play Love Marble.
‪"The rules of Love Marble."
‪"Players take turns rolling the dice
‪and move the number of spaces rolled."
‪"You must complete the mission
‪on the space you land on."
‪"Each player gets one pass."
‪-Cheers.
‪-It's the last night.
‪-Really?
‪-Find out how each other feel.
‪FIND OUT HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT EACH OTHER
‪ON THE FINAL NIGHT
‪I thought, "Something's going
‪to happen tonight."
‪"It's all going down tonight."
‪We were about to see the results
‪of everything that happened so far
‪and get a sense of what's what.
‪I was curious to see
‪what Ga-yeon would decide.
‪Even if I landed on a mission
‪to hold hands with someone,
‪I wouldn't have anyone to choose,
‪so I had mixed emotions.
‪We call it "sealing the deal," right?
‪Since it was the last night,
‪I thought it might be a chance
‪to seal the deal with Ga-yeon
‪and make it clear to the group as well.
‪It was like a game of Truth.
‪It could put us in a tough spot.
‪I saw what it says…
‪We're really going to be in trouble
‪if we do this.
‪I thought, "What do I do?"
‪I wasn't sure how I felt.
‪-We will now begin playing Love Marble.
‪-Let's go!
‪LET'S BEGIN LOVE MARBLE
‪Should we decide the order first?
‪No, let the king decide.
‪Let's go clockwise. I'll go first.
‪-Okay.
‪-All right.
‪DO-GEON
‪-That's a six.
‪-This won't be easy.
‪Yeah, the gray one.
‪One, two, three, four, five, six.
‪"Love Target Zone?"
‪"Pick anyone you wish
‪and ask two questions."
‪Pick one person?
‪-Can I ask anything?
‪-One person would be too obvious,
‪so pick two people.
‪-Okay, one question each.
‪-Okay.
‪I can't believe this is the first mission.
‪Kyung-ho.
‪Tell us
‪who takes first place in your heart?
‪-You want the reason?
‪-Yeah, that too.
‪That's a good one.
‪-Nice!
‪-Good going.
‪After talking to Ye-rim,
‪I wanted to know how Kyung-ho felt.
‪It's Ga-yeon.
‪-Why?
‪-My reason?
‪My heart dropped.
‪I realized he wanted to show
‪he was serious about her.
‪What's your reason?
‪I feel at ease with her.
‪I need a drink.
‪Seriously.
‪-This is so fun.
‪-I love it.
‪Yeah, it's so fun.
‪-Okay.
‪-Cool.
‪-Who next?
‪-Well played.
‪-Jung-min.
‪-Yeah?
‪Who is your current top pick, Jung-min?
‪Mine is Ga-yeon.
‪-What's your reason?
‪-My reason…
‪There are too many reasons.
‪But when we're together,
‪I don't feel awkward and I'm just myself.
‪I feel like my true self comes out.
‪-I feel totally at ease.
‪-Your reasons are so similar.
‪Right? They're similar.
‪I guess that's a part of Ga-yeon's charm.
‪YE-RIM
‪-Six.
‪-Six!
‪LOVE TARGET ZONE
‪-It's another six.
‪-Six keeps coming out.
‪We keep rolling sixes.
‪I want to ask Ga-yeon.
‪Who's your top pick?
‪This is so fun.
‪Hey, shall we get our drinks ready?
‪-I have to answer, right?
‪-Yeah.
‪-Or take a shot.
‪-But you have one pass.
‪-Will she use it?
‪-Maybe.
‪I'm sure Ga-yeon will pick me.
‪I kind of want to pass.
‪-I'll pass on this one.
‪-Okay.
‪Sure.
‪That made me a bit uneasy.
‪But I figured she didn't
‪want to upset Kyung-ho.
‪I didn't want to share my feelings
‪in front of everyone.
‪I just needed
‪to get out of that situation.
‪-Kyung-ho.
‪-Yes?
‪How open is your heart right now,
‪percentage-wise?
‪Do you get who I'm asking about?
‪Can you ask the question one more time?
‪How open is your heart, percentage-wise?
‪Open to who?
‪Who else would it be?
‪That's why I'm going this far
‪to explain myself.
‪I want you to open up to me
‪just a little bit more.
‪Okay. I won't close the door on you.
‪Thirty percent?
‪He said he was 30 percent open.
‪I think I was hoping he'd pick me
‪at least once.
‪GA-YEON
‪-Two.
‪-What's it say?
‪-Gosh.
‪-I can't see.
‪-I'll read it.
‪-It's intense.
‪"Say something flirty and do a love shot
‪with someone you gave
‪Heart Chips to yesterday,
‪or say something flirty and feed a snack
‪to the person you're interested in."
‪That's a fun one.
‪A snack?
‪Which one are you choosing?
‪A DRINK WITH ONE YOU GAVE HEARTS TO
‪OR A SNACK FOR ONE YOU'RE INTERESTED IN
‪I'll say something flirty and feed a snack
‪to the guy I'm interested in.
‪-Okay.
‪-All right.
‪Oh, man.
‪I think I'm interested in you.
‪-I see.
‪-That's how it is.
‪-Right.
‪-I see.
‪I need soju. Can you pour me a shot?
‪You look so down.
‪You must be craving some soju.
‪-Who's next?
‪-Next.
‪-It's getting serious.
‪-He's looking darker.
‪-That face should've come sooner.
‪-You know…
‪I went over it again in my mind.
‪If I were her
‪and Jung-min were my first choice,
‪I'd have picked the person
‪I gave the Heart Chips to.
‪Since she gave them to me.
‪The more I thought about it,
‪her picking Kyung-ho made no sense.
‪I wondered if she was still conflicted.
‪I thought I should choose the guy
‪I felt more drawn to at that moment.
‪It was really tough.
‪HA-YOON
‪"A nice drink with the person
‪you gave Black Hearts to."
‪Let's take a shot, Do-geon.
‪Are you serious?
‪-How come?
‪-Wow.
‪I had my reasons.
‪AS PART OF THE PLOT,
‪HA-YOON GAVE BLACK HEARTS TO DO-GEON
‪Is that so? I get it.
‪-I'm sorry.
‪-"I had my reasons."
‪I understand.
‪-I'm sorry. You know that, right?
‪-But why?
‪I had no choice but to use
‪Black Hearts on Do-geon.
‪-Here I go.
‪-I was so surprised.
‪JUNG-MIN
‪It's a new mission.
‪ASK THE PERSON YOU THINK GAVE YOU
‪HEART CHIPS TO FEED YOU A SNACK
‪-Read it out loud.
‪-Feed me, too.
‪-What?
‪-Come on.
‪-Read it out loud first.
‪-Oh, please.
‪"Ask the person you think gave you
‪Heart Chips to feed you a snack."
‪Oh, gosh.
‪The snacks are selling like crazy.
‪-She's feeding a lot of mouths.
‪-Mother bird.
‪Next.
‪I partly did it to loosen up a bit.
‪But my head's a mess, honestly.
‪HYE-WON
‪"Share your most exciting moment
‪since you got here."
‪There was a time
‪when no one picked me.
‪But then I got a text
‪about a camping date.
‪I'm going.
‪So I ran out right away.
‪-That was the moment?
‪-Yeah.
‪The time your knight in shining armor
‪came to the rescue?
‪When I went to see him.
‪Ha-yoon's face just now…
‪Did he give birth to her?
‪Is he her dad?
‪"Does she mean me?"
‪The time your knight in shining armor
‪came to the rescue?
‪When I went to see him.
‪CHAE-RIN
‪-Three.
‪-What's it say? Read it out.
‪"Whisper one thing to the person
‪you gave Heart Chips to yesterday."
‪-"The person chosen must respond."
‪-They have to reply.
‪Unbelievable.
‪Okay.
‪Can you guys hear?
‪Let's make noise for them.
‪Slightly bang the table.
‪Call me ‪nuna‪.
‪You have to respond.
‪Nuna.
‪Why is she so excited?
‪-Because she's in love.
‪-She's so excited.
‪Nuna.
‪-Are you happy?
‪-Yeah.
‪There you go.
‪On my first date with Do-geon,
‪I told him to call me ‪nuna‪.
‪Call me‪ nuna‪.
‪Come on.
‪He looked at me like, "Not a chance."
‪So ever since then,
‪I was determined to make him say it.
‪"Call me ‪nuna‪."
‪It was seriously so much fun.
‪YE-RIM
‪-She's good.
‪-It's another six.
‪She might win…
‪Four, five, six.
‪-Need to sigh?
‪-That spot…
‪MOVE TO THE SEAT
‪NEXT TO THE PERSON YOU LIKE!
‪"Move to the seat
‪next to the person you like."
‪Next to them?
‪Change seats with Ga-yeon.
‪-Just switch.
‪-Switch.
‪-Want to switch seats with me?
‪-Sure.
‪Welcome.
‪I feel a bit dizzy.
‪She's back to her feeble self.
‪The feeble princess is back.
‪Okay!
‪Honestly, I really hesitated
‪because he was making
‪his feelings so obvious.
‪But it was our last night,
‪so I just took my shot.
‪KYUNG-HO
‪-Wow.
‪-No way.
‪-What is it?
‪-I can't see.
‪Read it out loud.
‪-What's it say?
‪-What is it?
‪"Interlock fingers with the person
‪you gave Heart Chips to yesterday
‪for one minute while playing the game."
‪How should I make room for you two?
‪-Should we switch?
‪-Yeah.
‪Let's keep playing.
‪-It's my turn, right?
‪-Yeah.
‪They switched again.
‪-She's at the very end.
‪-This is so cruel to Ye-rim.
‪-Yeah?
‪-I'll roll once you hold hands.
‪We're already holding hands.
‪Okay. Show us.
‪-Put your hands on the table.
‪-Why do this to us?
‪All right.
‪-There you go.
‪-Good.
‪It was obvious that Kyung-ho was trying
‪to make his feelings clear.
‪I think I'd given up.
‪-I need a drink.
‪-Are you okay?
‪Set the timer for one minute.
‪I'll set it.
‪Earlier, on our secret date,
‪I told her to try holding hands
‪with both me and Kyung-ho and compare.
‪Look.
‪Hold hands like this.
‪Hold hands with me…
‪-And Kyung-ho?
‪-…and with Kyung-ho too.
‪You're insane. You want me
‪to hold hands with Kyung-ho?
‪You'll feel it for yourself.
‪What do you think about my strategy?
‪And crazy enough, it came up.
‪But I could get a chance
‪to hold her hand on my next turn
‪and make her heart race more.
‪HA-YOON
‪-Six?
‪-Six spaces.
‪One, two, three, four, five, six.
‪"Take a nice drink with the one
‪you gave Black Hearts to."
‪-It's because your piece is black.
‪-Yesterday, right?
‪His fingers are interlocked.
‪"His fingers are interlocked."
‪-The one I gave Black Hearts to yesterday.
‪-Which one is it?
‪-We need to take a shot.
‪-So funny.
‪-Kyung-ho.
‪-It's me, isn't it?
‪Want to take the hit instead?
‪Yeah, I will.
‪You gave them to me?
‪But he can drink it for you.
‪It's not against the rules.
‪Pour me just a bit more.
‪I did it by accident.
‪-I didn't mean to.
‪-Yeah.
‪-Your fingers slipped.
‪-Exactly.
‪-I'm sorry.
‪-Done.
‪DO-GEON
‪-What is it?
‪-Read it out.
‪"Say something flirty and do a love shot
‪with someone you gave
‪Heart Chips to yesterday,
‪or say something flirty and feed a snack
‪to the person you're interested in."
‪Let's have a drink together
‪at Gireum Station tomorrow.
‪Gosh.
‪Mission passed.
‪-You pass.
‪-Well done.
‪You pass with flying colors.
‪Next.
‪I knew tomorrow wouldn't be
‪the last time I'd see Chae-rin.
‪I wanted to see her again
‪in the near future.
‪CHAE-RIN
‪"Ask the one you think gave you
‪Heart Chips to feed you a snack."
‪You two are doing it all.
‪What are you doing?
‪Do-geon's so funny.
‪-What?
‪-The booze is sweet today.
‪-I need a drink too.
‪-They're happy.
‪Let's push their table away.
‪It was such a clever move.
‪I really liked that about him.
‪"Oh, he knows how to joke."
‪He's more fun than I thought.
‪I liked that.
‪I found her adorable
‪and my heart raced a bit.
‪-They're so cute.
‪-They are cute.
‪They're a comfort couple.
‪-So cute.
‪-We need a couple like that.
‪Yeah, they're adorable.
‪GA-YEON
‪-Three.
‪-What is it?
‪"Interlock fingers with the person
‪you gave Hearts Chips to yesterday
‪for one minute while playing the game."
‪LAST NIGHT, HEART CHIP VOTE
‪I thought we can go on our date
‪if we make Jung-min king.
‪GA-YEON GAVE JUNG-MIN 163 HEART CHIPS
‪And since I had fun
‪on my date with Kyung-ho,
‪I made that known to him.
‪GA-YEON GAVE KYUNG-HO 6 HEARTS
‪GA-YEON GAVE HEARTS
‪TO BOTH JUNG-MIN AND KYUNG-HO
‪I need to pick one person, right?
‪Want to hold hands with two people?
‪No, I was just asking.
‪How should we go about this?
‪-What do I do?
‪-She should decide.
‪-Let her pick?
‪-I think that's only right.
‪-Sure.
‪-Let her decide.
‪-What should I do?
‪-Want to switch?
‪Okay.
‪Just put your hands on the table.
‪-Okay.
‪-Yeah.
‪I'll pick the person
‪I gave the most Heart Chips to,
‪which is Jung-min.
‪I thought, "Is it over for me?"
‪I wasn't relaxed,
‪but I was confident that she'd choose me.
‪I'll roll now.
‪KYUNG-HO
‪"Answer yes or no if you decided
‪on your final choice."
‪Yes.
‪Yes, I have.
‪I had to be honest.
‪I saw it coming.
‪He confirmed that he liked her.
‪I thought, "So this is how it is."
‪It just became clear.
‪There was no room
‪for me in his heart anymore.
‪JUNG-MIN
‪-Move next to the person you like.
‪-Right.
‪-Gosh.
‪-Get over here.
‪What was the mission?
‪-Move next to the person you like.
‪-Change seats.
‪I see.
‪Here you go.
‪Is it my turn?
‪Kyung-ho and Jung-min both
‪made their feelings for me obvious.
‪I knew I had to choose between them.
‪It was really tough.
‪DO-GEON
‪Two.
‪"Move to the seat
‪next to the person you like."
‪Okay.
‪She's like, "Okay."
‪Yes!
‪YE-RIM
‪Three.
‪What's it say?
‪"Touch the part of the face
‪you find most attractive
‪on the person you like most."
‪Part of the face…
‪Touch?
‪I thought,
‪"He must feel so uncomfortable."
‪"Is it okay for me to do this?"
‪Part of the face…
‪-Can I touch?
‪-Of course.
‪Get up if you think it's you.
‪He gave me the go ahead,
‪so I touched his eyes.
‪He has pretty eyes.
‪But I had to really think about it.
‪Because he has lot of nice features,
‪It was hard to choose,
‪and I was a bit nervous.
‪I practically poked him.
‪GA-YEON
‪"Share your most exciting moment
‪since you got here."
‪Come on.
‪I couldn't return both their affections.
‪Someone was bound to get hurt.
‪That's how the game worked.
‪For me, it was today.
‪When I got back to the house
‪after the secret conversation.
‪Why?
‪My feelings kept going back and forth…
‪I was really torn…
‪But I think
‪that's when I made my decesion.
‪It was really super tough.
‪Kyung-ho made it really clear to everyone
‪that I was his final choice.
‪So I did the same.
‪Just the two of us, able to focus
‪on each other…
‪It was a good chance.
‪-All right.
‪-Okay.
‪I wasn't feeling well
‪after the secret date,
‪and it was such a critical moment.
‪So I thought, "I'm in trouble."
‪"Did something happen?"
‪DO-GEON
‪Two.
‪"Whisper one thing to the person
‪you gave Heart Chips to yesterday."
‪You have to respond.
‪Can you do this?
‪Will you still see me even after we leave?
‪-Did you catch that?
‪-Yeah.
‪All right.
‪You have to respond.
‪Okay.
‪I must be crazy.
‪It's so funny.
‪I felt so shy.
‪I should have replied more sweetly,
‪but I was just like, "Okay."
‪And then I regretted it.
‪He was probably a bit taken aback.
‪Okay.
‪-"Okay."
‪-I wonder what he said.
‪-Six.
‪-Which one's mine? The red one.
‪GA-YEON
‪"Pick one person and ask them
‪what they think of you."
‪"The chosen person has to respond."
‪That's a good one.
‪I pick Kyung-ho.
‪What do you think about me?
‪You're pretty.
‪Next player.
‪-It's you.
‪-Yeah.
‪-Is it not?
‪-Isn't it Chae-rin?
‪Oh, right.
‪I was dumbfounded.
‪My face kept getting darker.
‪I didn't really feel like smiling,
‪and even if I did,
‪you could totally tell it was forced.
‪It was hard.
‪YE-RIM
‪"Interlock fingers with the person
‪you gave Heart Chips to yesterday
‪for one minute while playing the game."
‪Gosh, this is fun.
‪Do I have to?
‪-Of course.
‪-Yeah, you do.
‪It must be warm.
‪We had to hold hands for a mission
‪on the first night.
‪It brought back that memory.
‪At that time, it felt really sincere.
‪Please go on a date with me tomorrow.
‪Okay. I'll go on a date with you.
‪But this time,
‪he didn't seem to feel anything at all.
‪He was really cold.
‪They were so cute together
‪in the beginning.
‪How many days has it been?
‪-Four days.
‪-It's only the fourth day.
‪How can someone change
‪that much in just four days?
‪Remember "Blind Date in a Bed?"
‪Oh, you're right.
‪-This is the fun of dating shows.
‪-Right.
‪GA-YEON
‪"Answer with O or X
‪if you have decided on your final choice."
‪Have you made your choice?
‪Even though I was happy about it,
‪I couldn't really show it
‪in that situation.
‪I was dancing on the inside.
‪"What do I do?"
‪"She's changed her mind to Kyung-ho."
‪I felt disappointed, and sad,
‪and angry, and betrayed.
‪I felt a jumble of emotions.
‪Jung-min must feel so betrayed.
‪Ye-rim felt betrayed
‪after only flirting for a day.
‪-They flirted for four days.
‪-Yeah. It's four days.
‪-She was all in for four days.
‪-Up until the last minute.
‪Exactly.
‪-Toilet break.
‪-I'll be back.
‪-Me too.
‪-Let's go.
‪I feel like
‪I should have been upfront
‪before we played this game.
‪Letting him find out like this…
‪-Do you feel bad?
‪-Yeah.
‪I feel bad for what I put him through…
‪What about Ye-rim?
‪Let's just get back for now.
‪Who's next?
‪GA-YEON
‪Three.
‪"Interlock fingers with the person
‪you gave Heart Chips to yesterday
‪for one minute while playing the game."
‪-Come on.
‪-Wow.
‪I want to say something.
‪Can I say it?
‪-Yeah.
‪-Of course.
‪I felt really torn earlier.
‪I wanted to talk to the person
‪I was conflicted about before this.
‪But he had to find out through this game
‪before I could tell him.
‪So I feel really bad.
‪So, if that person
‪feels really hurt,
‪I'm sorry.
‪I just wanted to say that.
‪Ga-yeon had to speak up to the group
‪before she could organize her thoughts.
‪I felt bad for her.
‪INTERLOCK FINGERS WITH THE PERSON
‪YOU GAVE HEART CHIPS TO
‪-Is that right?
‪-Yeah.
‪-Want to switch seats?
‪-Let's do that.
‪-I think that'd be better.
‪I found out through the game.
‪But honestly, I wasn't mad about that.
‪I was upset about the fact
‪that she didn't choose me.
‪The only time we spent apart
‪was after the secret conversation,
‪and I didn't expect her
‪to change her mind in such a short time.
‪JUNG-MIN
‪Three.
‪LOVE TARGET ZONE
‪It was bound to come up.
‪Why did your top pick
‪change from me to Kyung-ho?
‪It wasn't because
‪I wanted to know the reason.
‪It was more like, "How could you?"
‪Kind of like…
‪I think I let my emotions get
‪the better of me in that moment.
‪Logically, you were my first choice.
‪But I felt very drawn to Kyung-ho.
‪And I think
‪the strong pull I felt toward him
‪made me change my mind.
‪I think it helped me
‪make my mind up quicker.
‪I thought I should only choose Kyung-ho
‪if I was 90% sure about him,
‪but I realized he was the right choice
‪if I liked him even just 5% more.
‪I got chills.
‪She's been saying he was
‪her first choice romantically,
‪but she didn't mean it
‪in terms of attraction.
‪-She meant logically.
‪-Logic versus emotion.
‪-Basically--
‪-She's been mixing them up?
‪Listen.
‪She meant romantic attraction
‪when she said it,
‪but far in the back of her mind,
‪it was more a matter
‪of logic versus emotion, T and F.
‪Logically, he was the right choice.
‪But emotionally, it was Kyung-ho.
‪I don't know--
‪-That's what happened.
‪-I don't know anymore.
‪Hallelujah.
‪I want to ask Kyung-ho
‪the same question.
‪How did your feelings
‪suddenly change so much
‪in just a day or two?
‪I think it was a battle over
‪who was more entitled.
‪I didn't think I'd done anything wrong,
‪so I saw no reason to back down.
‪I answered him calmly.
‪First of all, it wasn't a big change.
‪I said from the start
‪that I was interested in both women.
‪There hasn't been a drastic change.
‪When I talked to both women,
‪this is how I felt.
‪I'm sure it's the same for everyone here.
‪We're all just drawn to certain people.
‪It's the same for me.
‪All right.
‪It felt like what he'd said to me
‪didn't mean much anymore.
‪What he said in front
‪of Ga-yeon and everyone
‪made the things he said to me
‪lose some weight.
‪That was disappointing.
‪-One.
‪-Aren't you going to bang the table?
‪-Okay.
‪Ga-yeon ‪nuna‪.
‪We opened up so much to the group
‪that I didn't worry too much after that.
‪-Close your eyes.
‪-Close my eyes?
‪They're shut, right?
‪Why close her eyes?
‪I was on edge the whole time.
‪They kept rubbing salt in the wound.
‪One blow after another.
‪I didn't really want to see
‪them flirt together,
‪so that was really tough.
‪Love Marble has ended.
‪I think it's my first time
‪drinking in years.
‪-Years?
‪-Yeah.
‪I think it's been about four years.
‪-Love Marble? Is that what it's called?
‪-Yeah.
‪It really sucked, honestly.
‪I had so much fun.
‪-Same.
‪-It was so fun.
‪It was really fun.
‪We got a text.
‪-Time for the Heart Chip Vote.
‪-We need to go.
‪THE FINAL HEART CHIP VOTE STARTS NOW.
‪PLEASE GO TO THE HEART ROOM.
‪YOU CAN ONLY USE THE HEART CHIPS
‪AND VOTE FOR JUST ONE PERSON
‪IF YOU USE UP YOUR REMAINING HEART CHIPS,
‪YOU MUST CONFESS YOUR FEELINGS TOMORROW
‪I think
‪there are some who are
‪contemplating leaving some or not.
‪If you leave just one,
‪it means you're not confessing…
‪I guess some people might do that.
‪Thanks for everything, Do-geon.
‪We both expressed our feelings
‪and felt pretty secure about each other,
‪so I wrote, "Let's meet up in Hyehwa."
‪Thank you for showing me how you felt,
‪but I'm too shy to confess my feelings.
‪I think I simply wrote,
‪"See you tomorrow."
‪"Let's talk in person."
‪PARK GA-YEON
‪ENTERS THE HEART ROOM
‪KANG KYUNG-HO
‪PARK JUNG-MIN
‪ENTERS THE HEART ROOM
‪I had no one to give my chips.
‪I contemplated what to do.
‪PARK JUNG-MIN COMPLETED VOTING
‪Did he use them all up?
‪LEE YE-RIM
‪ENTERS THE HEART ROOM
‪I wasn't sure if I should vote
‪since I'd have to confess the next day
‪if I used up my chips.
‪He'd already made his feelings clear,
‪so confessing my feelings
‪wouldn't be easy.
‪Because I was disappointed in him,
‪he wasn't worth giving my heart.
‪It seemed like he couldn't
‪appreciate what I had to offer.
‪I wished I hadn't fallen for him
‪and given so much.
‪I felt torn again.
‪LEE YE-RIM COMPLETED VOTING
‪The final Heart Chip vote has ended.
‪Jung-min.
‪Jung-min?
‪-Do you want to talk?
‪-Yeah.
‪It's okay.
‪To be honest,
‪even just before the game,
‪I was struggling to decide.
‪I was really conflicted.
‪But when I got back to the house,
‪Kyung-ho was the only one here,
‪so we got to talking.
‪And at the time,
‪I didn't know what to think.
‪I wasn't sure what I was feeling.
‪I was really confused.
‪But before I could tell you,
‪we ended up playing that game.
‪Without meaning to, in front of everyone,
‪we ended up in this weird situation.
‪-That didn't bother me that much.
‪-Then what?
‪I'm more curious why
‪you moved on to Kyung-ho.
‪I think I was in denial
‪about my feelings for him.
‪I think I was too confident
‪about my relationship with you.
‪I'm a bit sad and disappointed,
‪and a little resentful.
‪But what can I do? I have to accept it.
‪I don't want you to feel too sorry.
‪-Because it's okay.
‪-The reason I'm sorry
‪isn't because I changed my mind.
‪It's because I let you find out
‪through that game.
‪-I totally understand that.
‪-Really?
‪It's a tough thing to bring up.
‪You told me as soon as you could.
‪I wanted to talk you around
‪and turn the tables if I'm honest,
‪even up until a second ago.
‪But when you came in here
‪wanting to talk to me first,
‪I realized your mind's made up.
‪Honestly, I was
‪a bit confused
‪even while we were playing the game.
‪No, really. I mean it.
‪I kept changing my mind
‪about which way to go
‪the whole time we were playing.
‪But even so,
‪I couldn't pick you for one thing
‪and then Kyung-ho for another.
‪That would be wrong.
‪You worried how it would look
‪if you kept switching during the game?
‪Well, I thought it wasn't
‪the right thing to do.
‪I felt like I had to hurry
‪in that moment
‪and quickly make my mind up.
‪You made your choice before the game.
‪No, I…
‪-I didn't.
‪-I wanted to ask you this.
‪Was the moment you made your mind up
‪after the secret date,
‪the moment you got back?
‪Ye-rim told me
‪that she saw you together.
‪She said,
‪"Looks like we'll both leave here alone."
‪He's saying her story doesn't add up.
‪You know that,
‪when someone who's always smiley
‪suddenly gets serious,
‪-it's pretty scary.
‪-It's scary.
‪-It's really scary right now.
‪-Yeah.
‪You already made your mind up.
‪Why blame it on the game?
‪-No, I--
‪-As if you didn't know.
‪-No, the thing is…
‪-Yeah?
‪-Well--
‪-Be honest.
‪I'm being completely honest.
‪At the time, I hadn't decided who to pick
‪as my final choice.
‪I just felt more swayed toward Kyung-ho.
‪But then during the game,
‪I felt like I needed
‪to make my choice in that moment
‪and make my feelings clear
‪toward just one person.
‪Or else you'd both be confused
‪or the situation would get weird.
‪And since I was leaning more
‪toward Kyung-ho…
‪-Good job.
‪-…that's what happened.
‪I get it.
‪I wondered
‪if I could develop feelings for anyone
‪in such a short time.
‪-And you did.
‪-I ended up
‪-feeling a lot.
‪-Your feelings came, went, and changed.
‪-They turned hot and cold.
‪-But also,
‪it's been really hard.
‪I keep wondering
‪if I'm doing the right thing.
‪I'm so confused.
‪I think I was a little aggressive.
‪And I think I clearly said
‪that I resented her.
‪I asked her questions
‪I already knew the answer to.
‪What's done was done
‪and there was no changing it.
‪I dragged it out for no reason
‪and got too emotional.
‪When I realized that,
‪I put a stop to the conversation.
‪I really liked you a lot.
‪I didn't tell you this on the secret date,
‪but I'm not in a stable place right now.
‪Financially or with my job
‪as a diving instructor.
‪So I was self-conscious about that.
‪I knew you wanted someone secure…
‪If we'd dated, I might not have been able
‪to give you what you wanted…
‪That's something I thought about.
‪Thanks for making me feel all this.
‪Oh, man.
‪I appreciate it.
‪My favorite memory is taking selfies
‪in our matching outfits.
‪It's the same for me.
‪-Yeah.
‪-So to be honest,
‪when I answered the question
‪about the most exciting moment,
‪I don't think I was completely genuine.
‪I was going to question it but didn't.
‪Because your mind seemed made up.
‪All right.
‪Well done.
‪You're so popular.
‪I'm fine.
‪I'll get over this on my own.
‪I feel a bit…
‪I hope you don't get hurt this time.
‪She said she's been hurt
‪by the guys she was drawn to.
‪She's doing it again,
‪-so he hopes she won't get hurt.
‪-By Kyung-ho.
‪Wow, to the very end.
‪How did they all develop
‪such deep feelings?
‪Right.
‪Usually, there are two guys and girls
‪who aren't interested in anyone
‪-and just keep wandering.
‪-Right.
‪-There's always a wanderer.
‪-Totally.
‪-Always!
‪-But not this time!
‪-They're all so sincere.
‪-Yeah.
‪From a viewer's perspective,
‪it's so much fun.
‪-I really appreciate it. Here's why.
‪-I'm so thankful.
‪No joke, this moment has makes me
‪so proud of our show.
‪It's only been four days and--
‪-Tears, fighting, and drama.
‪-So much crying.
‪You'd think they've been dating
‪for months.
‪Yeah. Gosh.
‪It's here.
‪The glamping tent will be open
‪to everyone until tomorrow morning.
‪It says you can only use it
‪with one person of the opposite sex.
‪So I guess
‪anyone who wants a bit more
‪lovey-dovey time can do so.
‪I think we can choose freely.
‪Aren't you curious?
‪-About what?
‪-Glamping.
‪Glamping?
‪Is it the last date?
‪-This? I think so.
‪-Yeah.
‪Is everyone here?
‪-You're all here.
‪-Yeah.
‪You're drinking again?
‪Aren't you drinking too much?
‪It's our last night.
‪How much have you had?
‪-I think about three bottles?
‪-Three bottles?
‪-Stop drinking.
‪-Two or three.
‪Come on.
‪I think you're drinking too much.
‪It's fine. I'll stick close to Ha-yoon.
‪-That's not the issue.
‪-Go have fun with Kyung-ho.
‪-What?
‪-Isn't he waiting for you?
‪No, he's not.
‪He might be.
‪He's not.
‪As we discussed,
‪I get it.
‪I got the message.
‪It's not that I didn't notice,
‪but I tried not to look.
‪I felt like Ga-yeon and Jung-min
‪needed some closure,
‪so I kept my distance.
‪You're here because you're sorry, right?
‪No. That's not why.
‪-Yes, it is.
‪-No, it's not.
‪It's so obvious.
‪That's not it.
‪Then why are you here?
‪-Just.
‪-Just?
‪Ye-rim is so strong-minded.
‪Why?
‪-Because she's not bothered?
‪-What?
‪Because she's handling
‪the situation so well?
‪Yeah, she's in a similar situation to me.
‪Of course, she was in this position first.
‪-Which is better?
‪-What do you mean?
‪Finding out your feelings
‪are one-sided before the final vote
‪or finding out after the first day?
‪I'd rather find out at the end
‪and be blindsided.
‪-Me too. I'd rather find out at the end.
‪-Right?
‪I couldn't handle
‪being in Ye-rim's position.
‪I couldn't endure several days of that.
‪I'd rather have fun
‪and suffer a bit at the end,
‪have a drink, and forget.
‪-Say goodbye, call a taxi, and go home.
‪-Exactly.
‪Yeah, she's in a similar situation to me.
‪Of course, she was in this position first.
‪I'm just going through it now.
‪I think I felt a bit uncomfortable
‪by his changed attitude.
‪I obviously didn't expect him
‪to be nice to me after I hurt him.
‪But he was acting so differently
‪that it was hard to be around him.
‪This is so frustrating.
‪Me too.
‪Ga-yeon, I…
‪-What's wrong?
‪-Why's Jung-min acting like that?
‪Like what?
‪-Jung-min.
‪-Yeah?
‪I don't know. It's tough.
‪Did I tease her too much?
‪Maybe I did.
‪Hey, Kyung-ho.
‪I think I was a bit too harsh.
‪You should talk to her.
‪I'm sorry.
‪Not at all.
‪He's leaving it to Kyung-ho.
‪What's wrong with you? What are you doing?
‪Shouldn't I give her some time alone?
‪And also…
‪I don't know what this is,
‪-but during the game,
‪-Yeah?
‪remember I held both their hands?
‪But I think my heart raced more
‪when Jung-min held my hand…
‪I want to come in.
‪Should I leave?
‪No, it's fine.
‪Sit over there.
‪Can I sit here?
‪Seriously.
‪Did you not see what just happened?
‪You didn't see, did you?
‪I tried not to look on purpose.
‪He kept saying, "Go to Kyung-ho."
‪"Go and have fun with him.
‪He's waiting for you."
‪He kept making it
‪really uncomfortable.
‪I mean,
‪why can't he accept it?
‪From his perspective,
‪it's obviously disappointing.
‪He told me this.
‪Ye-rim found out yesterday…
‪but he only just found out.
‪But the way he's expressing his anger…
‪I don't know if it's the alcohol talking,
‪but I feel like he's crossing a line.
‪I get how you feel…
‪but Ga-yeon
‪you should just accept
‪how he's acting too.
‪What can you do? That's how he feels.
‪You can't control his emotions.
‪Jung-min has a right to be angry
‪about the choice you made.
‪If you push him to get over it,
‪that's selfish.
‪Bravo!
‪-Hye-won!
‪The queen is right!
‪The queen is different!
‪This is crazy.
‪-So good.
‪-She's doing our job for us.
‪So this is why people
‪watch reaction videos.
‪-How did she say exactly what I wanted?
‪-She's so wise and insightful.
‪-You're right.
‪-Yeah.
‪I think he's still drinking too much.
‪Just let him.
‪That's what he wants to do.
‪Stop trying to solve things.
‪-He'll be fine when he sobers up, right?
‪-Huh?
‪-He's just drunk, right?
‪-Of course.
‪Yeah. This isn't him.
‪-Right, he's not…
‪-He's not the Jung-min I know.
‪Ye-rim, you're really strong.
‪-Seriously.
‪-Did something happen?
‪I think I was
‪-a bit too harsh on her.
‪-Really?
‪That you were disappointed?
‪Yeah, that kind of thing.
‪I feel a bit bad,
‪seeing how she was just now.
‪I just blurted things out
‪without meaning to.
‪I suddenly feel really bad.
‪Now that I'm in your position…
‪-I felt that way yesterday.
‪-Yeah.
‪It is annoying, though.
‪Kyung-ho
‪went to you,
‪then he slid over to Ga-yeon.
‪He opened up to both of you.
‪Yeah.
‪This is really irritating.
‪What can I do?
‪You liked him,
‪and Ga-yeon liked him.
‪And I was on the sideline.
‪And you were by Kyung-ho's side.
‪Odd one out, odd one out.
‪This is really irritating.
‪I thought I had pretty high self-esteem.
‪Yeah.
‪It's even more irritating
‪because of Kyung-ho.
‪I feel petty for no good reason.
‪I felt the same way.
‪I resented Ga-yeon too.
‪But…
‪Jung-min may have felt confident,
‪but that was on him, right?
‪Did you give him reason to feel that?
‪When he said he was sure about us,
‪I didn't deny it.
‪So he might have felt
‪I was returning his feelings.
‪That's probably how he felt.
‪He probably felt quite secure,
‪-and that turned into certainty.
‪-You're right.
‪But I don't think
‪you should beat yourself…
‪-No, you don't.
‪-Not at all.
‪One, two, three.
‪-You don't need to beat yourself up.
‪-Don't beat yourself up.
‪-I just…
‪-The one thing I want to say to you is
‪that it's not like you didn't do enough
‪or did anything wrong.
‪-Yeah. I know that for sure.
‪-Yeah. You know that, right?
‪But at least Ga-yeon
‪went to talk to you
‪as soon as we got back.
‪I think she deserves credit for that,
‪unlike someone else.
‪Where are they? Are they in the tent?
‪Her and Kyung-ho?
‪Should I go check?
‪Did you want to go to bed, Ye-rim?
‪Where did Chae-rin go?
‪-Her and Do-geon.
‪-Do-geon?
‪-Maybe the tent?
‪-The tent?
‪CHAE-RIN AND DO-GEON
‪DISCUSS THEIR IDEAL TYPES
‪Whoever I'm into is my type.
‪I don't really have a specific ideal type.
‪-But one thing is for sure.
‪-What?
‪Personality.
‪-Oh, someone who's outgoing and chatty?
‪-If our personalities don't match,
‪I can't date them,
‪even if they are physically my type.
‪In terms of faces,
‪they just need to be pretty.
‪You're pretty.
‪-Me?
‪-Yeah.
‪Of course, I am.
‪Do I fit your ideal type?
‪For me,
‪I like an edge-of-tofu face.
‪"Edge-of-tofu."
‪Why does everyone on this show
‪like edge-of-tofu faces so much?
‪I'm scared.
‪Was it Ji-young who liked
‪an edge-of-tofu face?
‪Scary.
‪That actually works?
‪I like an edge-of-tofu face.
‪"Edge-of-tofu."
‪What is an edge-of-tofu face?
‪Come in.
‪-Can I come in?
‪-Yeah.
‪Do you know what an edge-of-tofu type is?
‪-What?
‪-An edge-of-tofu type.
‪-Edge-of-tofu type?
‪-Yeah.
‪Isn't that you?
‪It's when you have an angular look
‪like the edges of a tofu block.
‪Spot on. A SNU graduate, indeed.
‪Anyway, it's you, right?
‪She means you, right?
‪-I guess so.
‪-Yeah. Okay.
‪Have a nice chat.
‪Impressive.
‪Who is that guy?
‪-I love Ha-yoon.
‪-He's great.
‪When you all walked in one by one,
‪you came in last, right?
‪But they were a bit intense
‪and a bit too much.
‪I couldn't figure out the last one…
‪Then I saw your edge-of-tofu face.
‪I was like, "Is this destiny?"
‪"This is the guy."
‪But honestly,
‪I wasn't sure if I'd fall for anyone
‪on this show.
‪-Totally.
‪-Yeah.
‪-I was skeptical.
‪-Same.
‪But then I came here and met you.
‪I mean, what?
‪Come again?
‪I like him more as time goes on.
‪Ha-yoon and Hye-won split up
‪to counsel different people.
‪They'll reunite in the tent later.
‪-"Honey, how did it go with you?"
‪-You're right.
‪"This is the story I heard."
‪"The kids under my care
‪are really angry right now."
‪"I get where they're coming from."
‪-"Here's what I think."
‪-They're such a secure couple.
‪I can hear everything.
‪I hear Kyung-ho's voice
‪and Ga-yeon's voice.
‪Does it make you uncomfortable?
‪It freaking sucks.
‪You understand how I feel, right?
‪I do understand, honestly.
‪The situation sucks.
‪I'm drunk.
‪Did they enjoy the tent?
‪-Do-geon and--
‪-Did they go?
‪Weren't they in the tent
‪when Ye-rim came looking for them?
‪NO ONE'S USED IT YET
‪Should we go?
‪Do you want to?
‪Go on.
‪-See you later.
‪-Okay.
‪Have fun.
‪I wanted the two of us to have a chat,
‪being the last night and all.
‪I'm so annoyed.
‪Let's have one final drink.
‪So we made use of the tent.
‪-Inside?
‪-No.
‪Chairs?
‪-Is it warm?
‪-No.
‪-Oh, it is warm.
‪-It's warm.
‪Let's zip this up.
‪How did you know to do that?
‪-I was here before.
‪-Oh, right.
‪Gosh, how is it so warm?
‪-It's warm.
‪-Yeah, it's nice.
‪-It's all over.
‪-Tell me about it.
‪I wished we had more time
‪up until yesterday.
‪I don't feel like that at all now.
‪This is enough.
‪Your hands are so big.
‪Maybe your hands are small.
‪I do have really small hands.
‪That could be why.
‪For the last five days…
‪"Long five days?"
‪-Last five days.
‪-Oh, last five days…
‪I'm really thankful.
‪Me too.
‪We need to sleep. Oh, that's right.
‪How should we do this?
‪There's three of us.
‪Did Ga-yeon go to the tent?
‪Won't the two sleep there?
‪Are you going to bed?
‪They're in the tent.
‪You can hear everything.
‪What?
‪Just go to bed.
‪CHAE-RIN AND DO-GEON COME OUTSIDE
‪THE TENT IS ALREADY ZIPPED UP
‪They closed the flap.
‪So that's how you close it.
‪It's zipped up?
‪Unbelievable.
‪Did Ga-yeon and Kyung-ho go out?
‪Yeah.
‪-To the tent?
‪-For real?
‪Yeah.
‪What about that poor guy?
‪It was Jung-min who told me.
‪-What?
‪-Jung-min told me.
‪-See? We should have taken it first.
‪-Right.
‪Poor Jung-min.
‪-Maybe we really should have left earlier.
‪-Right.
‪Why did they go to the tent?
‪Hurry and go to bed.
‪-You hurry.
‪-Okay.
‪Let's just sleep in here together.
‪No.
‪Go to bed.
‪See you tomorrow.
‪-Isn't it all sorted out now?
‪-Yeah.
‪Jung-min too.
‪You think it's sorted?
‪I'm asking if it's sorted.
‪Right now?
‪Yeah.
‪My feelings?
‪Didn't you talk everything out?
‪-Yeah, we did.
‪-Then…
‪I said everything I wanted.
‪So there's nothing more you can do, right?
‪-Really?
‪-I handled it well.
‪-How?
‪-Just…
‪-You were smart about it?
‪-Yeah.
‪-All in the palm of your hand.
‪It went exactly as I expected.
‪I talked about this with Do-geon,
‪but it was over
‪when she touched my eye.
‪-Huh?
‪-When she touched my eye,
‪that ended it.
‪What do you mean?
‪Here.
‪I don't remember who made the first move,
‪but we ended up holding hands.
‪But rather than holding hands like this,
‪holding it like this
‪makes my heart race more.
‪All ticklish.
‪I did, but…
‪I had butterflies
‪around Ga-yeon the whole time.
‪My heart fluttered.
‪I didn't know.
‪I thought I was being really smart,
‪but nothing worked out the way I wanted.
‪Everything went my way.
‪Impressive. You're amazing.
‪-I am, aren't I?
‪-Yeah.
‪It didn't feel like this
‪when I came here with Do-geon.
‪When you came here with Do-geon?
‪I really hated that tent.
‪Do-geon and I laid down
‪as far apart as possible.
‪But Kyung-ho and I were
‪really close together.
‪We weren't right up against each other,
‪but we only left a small gap.
‪I told Kyung-ho
‪that I don't get physical with guys
‪unless I'm dating them.
‪We're touching now.
‪Points deducted.
‪Right.
‪I think it's important
‪when it comes to things
‪like physical touch.
‪Because it can actually
‪make you grow closer.
‪What are you going to do?
‪I'm still going to hold it.
‪Okay.
‪I try to be pretty disciplined,
‪but that's not so easy
‪when it comes to love.
‪I really want to be
‪a self-controlled person.
‪Yeah?
‪But
‪I'm failing.
‪I tend to lose my head a little
‪in that kind of setting.
‪With that kind of scent
‪and atmosphere.
‪I can't control myself.
‪It would be weird if you could.
‪It's impossible.
‪I thought I'd be able to.
‪How many times did you say
‪your head hurt over the last two days?
‪About 40 times?
‪I think it was about 100 times.
‪Really?
‪-No, you probably said it about 40 times.
‪-Yeah, 40.
‪How should we sleep?
‪I feel like she might not sleep out there.
‪They'll definitely sleep outside tonight.
‪-You think?
‪-Probably.
‪I don't think so. Let's check.
‪They already closed the tent.
‪-You're right.
‪-It's zipped up already.
‪-That's insane.
‪-I saw it.
‪They're giggling and flirting
‪inside the tent.
‪You can hear them so clearly,
‪being all lovey-dovey.
‪It's harder because
‪I didn't see it coming.
‪The fact that we're talking about this
‪means we need to get up.
‪Okay.
‪I said I wouldn't even
‪consider a younger guy.
‪Things don't always go the way you plan.
‪Yeah.
‪-You try.
‪-What?
‪Write something.
‪She wrote a message on my palm.
‪Jung?
‪What is it?
‪It felt like she wrote, "I like you."
‪So I said I wanted to try it too.
‪-Now, I'll try.
‪-Okay.
‪-This is the bottom.
‪I wrote, "Me too."
‪You could do it with me.
‪Don't you want to?
‪I do.
‪So refreshing.
‪-I hear them so well.
‪-I know.
‪What?
‪-Oh, Hye-won.
‪-Sorry.
‪What is it?
‪The noise.
‪What noise?
‪-Oh, them talking?
‪-Yeah.
‪-You can't hear what they're saying.
‪-You can't make out what it is.
‪-You're really busy, right?
‪-What?
‪-With work.
‪-Work?
‪What's your schedule like back home?
‪It does get a bit busy
‪but I'll have plenty of time to meet up.
‪Really?
‪Yeah.
‪You're busy, right?
‪-Me?
‪-Yeah.
‪My schedule is super flexible.
‪As long as I get my work done.
‪-Performance-based?
‪-Yeah.
‪I'm someone
‪who needs to win no matter what
‪when it comes to work.
‪Did you win in here?
‪I lost. No, I won.
‪-What?
‪-No.
‪Did you happily lose?
‪There were a few unexpected twists,
‪but
‪it worked out the way I wanted.
‪I think it's getting brighter.
‪The sun must be rising.
‪What time is it?
‪You're falling asleep.
‪-I'm sleepy.
‪-Me too.
‪Should we sleep?
‪We should wash up.
‪We'll need to shower later anyway.
‪I know.
‪Let's get up for real now.
‪-We really have to get up.
‪-I can't be bothered.
‪I know, but we still need to get up.
‪I'm so…
‪I'll come back at 8 o'clock.
‪-Okay.
‪-Good night.
‪Okay.
‪-Just sleep here.
‪-What?
‪No, I can't.
‪I need to wash up.
‪-Come on. I worked hard to get up.
‪-Okay.
‪Get up.
‪Go on.
‪Bye.
‪The sun's up.
‪That's how…
‪we stayed up the whole night.
‪We knew we liked each other
‪when we were talking this time,
‪so I had butterflies.
‪It was fun and exciting.
‪We talked a lot.
‪We joked around a lot
‪and talked about some serious stuff.
‪It was very memorable.
‪FINAL CHOICE D-DAY
‪JUNG-MIN PUTS ON MAKEUP BY HIMSELF
‪Is Ga-yeon awake?
‪She didn't sleep.
‪SNEAKS A PEEK
‪THEY DON'T EVEN GREET EACH OTHER
‪JUNG-MIN COMES LOOKING FOR GA-YEON
‪Can you do my makeup one last time?
‪One last makeup session?
‪He didn't say a word to her
‪until just now.
‪It's the same as when Ye-rim said,
‪"Let's be friends."
‪-It's the same thing.
‪-He's doing the same thing.
‪-A bit later.
‪-Your last makeup session.
‪Did you drink a lot?
‪I'm hungover for the first time.
‪How much did you drink?
‪I'm not sure. Maybe four or five bottles.
‪By yourself?
‪With others.
‪-All done.
‪-Good.
‪-Thanks.
‪-Mhm.
‪It's here.
‪-What is it?
‪-What came?
‪"It's the day of the final decision."
‪"Confess how you feel."
‪The Final Stage
‪of the King of Hearts game.
‪The final choice vote will begin.
‪I had to come in first no matter what.
‪I try not to lose.
‪I always tried to win.
‪I'm going to make him mine.
‪I won her over in the end.
‪Why should I be the one to give her up?
‪She's not an object,
‪but it's better if she's mine.
‪Our subjects always get what they want,
‪but did they find
‪the love they were after?
‪Participants who used up
‪all your Heart Chips,
‪please call out the name
‪of the person you want to confess to
‪and confess your feelings.
‪Jung Hye-won.
‪Bring your Heart Chips
‪and stand in front of the table.
‪I want
‪to confess my feelings
‪to Jung Ha-yoon
‪and give him my heart.
‪HYE-WON → HA-YOON
‪FINAL CHOICE
‪YESTERDAY NIGHT, FINAL HEART CHIP VOTE
‪I spent all my Heart Chips on Ha-yoon.
‪JUNG HYE-WON COMPLETED VOTING
‪ALL HEART CHIPS → HA-YOON
‪Ha-yoon's groundedness
‪served as fresh motivation to me.
‪He didn't put pressure on me,
‪but approached me like a calm lake.
‪Our queen.
‪Our secure participant.
‪But honestly, even putting his job aside,
‪I would pick Ha-yoon.
‪Ha-yoon.
‪I'm so grateful that you had the courage
‪to open up and share
‪your feelings with me.
‪Let's talk more in the real world.
‪He's an invaluable person to me.
‪Ha-yoon is such a great guy,
‪and I wondered if a guy like that
‪could handle someone like me.
‪Even I don't always know
‪where I'll pivot next.
‪So could a reserved guy like Ha-yoon
‪understand a girl like me?
‪If you want to confess your feelings,
‪after you confess,
‪put all your Heart Chips
‪into the glass jar.
‪If you wish to turn them down,
‪say your final goodbye
‪and return to your position.
‪Hye-won.
‪You were my choice
‪from the beginning to the end.
‪Once we get out, let's eat a lot
‪of good food and talk for hours.
‪I'm thankful too.
‪JUNG HA-YOON COMPLETED VOTING
‪ALL CHIPS → JUNG HYE-WON
‪Hye-won bounces around,
‪you never know where she'll go next.
‪I find that side of her really adorable.
‪I think I can keep her centered
‪so she doesn't bounce too far
‪in any one direction.
‪I'd like us to find that balance together.
‪HA-YOON → HYE-WON
‪FINAL CHOICE
‪Wow, congratulations.
‪Congratulations.
‪You are the first couple
‪of the first King of Hearts Game.
‪JUNG HYE-WON, JUNG HA-YOON
‪What now?
‪Even if we didn't meet in here,
‪if I had crossed her in the street
‪or met her randomly somewhere,
‪I'd still have found her attractive
‪and fallen for her.
‪We might go to a cafe.
‪Hye-won likes peppermint tea.
‪I can also enjoy tea together.
‪I think that's how we'll spend our time.
‪We'll have some more peppermint tea,
‪talk some more,
‪and see other sides of each other.
‪JUNG HA-YOON AND JUNG HYE-WON
‪FINAL COUPLE
‪Moon Chae-rin.
‪Bring your Heart Chips
‪and stand in front of the table.
‪I used all my remaining Heart Chips
‪on Park Do-geon.
‪I made him my final choice.
‪MOON CHAE-RIN COMPLETED VOTING
‪ALL CHIPS → PARK DO-GEON
‪I want to give my heart to Park Do-geon.
‪CHAE-RIN → DO-GEON
‪FINAL CHOICE
‪Honestly, when I found out
‪his age and profession,
‪I wasn't sure my feelings would grow.
‪I was a little worried.
‪But even though I hesitated,
‪he wasn't discouraged
‪and kept making his feelings really clear.
‪I think that's why my feelings
‪grew stronger rather than fade.
‪Do-geon.
‪The moments we spent talking
‪and just being together
‪made me happy and excited.
‪Thank you for everything.
‪My mind's made up.
‪When I fall for someone,
‪I only have eyes for them,
‪and Chae-rin's the one
‪who made me realize that.
‪We both expressed
‪our feelings to each other,
‪and I felt like we both
‪knew where we stood,
‪so I gave all my Heart Chips to Chae-rin.
‪I've never been interested
‪in anyone else but you
‪from the start until now.
‪You said you wanted to go bowling.
‪Let's go bowling together.
‪DO-GEON → CHAE-RIN
‪FINAL CHOICE
‪Whenever Chae-rin's feeling down,
‪dance "like JENNIE" for her, Do-geon.
‪Yeah, dance at Gireum Station
‪so I can watch too.
‪Congratulations.
‪You are the second couple
‪of the first King of Hearts game.
‪I'd just finished my military service
‪when this great opportunity came along
‪and I got to meet Moon Chae-rin.
‪I feel very blessed.
‪I felt like his feelings for me
‪were just as strong as mine were for him.
‪I was really thankful for that.
‪I hope we'll be just as excited
‪and comfortable even after we get out.
‪DO-GEON AND CHAE-RIN
‪FINAL COUPLE
‪-They suit each other so well.
‪-They're a great match.
‪-How nice.
‪-Lovely.
‪While I'm a little disappointed‪…
‪I feel like I did my best
‪in the time we were given,
‪so I don't think I have any regrets.
‪YE-RIM'S FINAL MESSAGE TO KYUNG-HO
‪I wrote, "I'm a better match
‪for you than Ga-yeon."
‪I'M A BETTER MATCH FOR YOU THAN GA-YEON
‪It was the final chance we had
‪to confess our feelings
‪and the last chance
‪to express what's on our minds,
‪and I wanted to be
‪true to my feelings to the end.
‪YE-RIM USED ALL HER HEART CHIPS LAST NIGHT
‪LEE YE-RIM
‪She did her best. No regrets.
‪That's a good thing.
‪For sure.
‪Lee Ye-rim.
‪Bring your Heart Chips
‪and stand in front of the table.
‪The person I want to give my heart
‪is Kang Kyung-ho.
‪YE-RIM → KYUNG-HO
‪FINAL CHOICE
‪As soon as I saw him,
‪I thought he was my ideal type.
‪And then he came over,
‪sat next to me, held my hand,
‪and asked me out on a date.
‪It was such a thrill,
‪and a happy memory for me.
‪I hope…
‪I'll be someone you remember.
‪Like you said, I'm a remarkable person,
‪so let's stay friends.
‪If you wish to turn them down,
‪say your final goodbye
‪and return to your position.
‪If you want to confess your feelings,
‪after you confess,
‪put all your Heart Chips
‪into the glass jar.
‪You really are a remarkable person
‪and I don't think that will change.
‪Let's be friends.
‪What just happened?
‪Did he choke up?
‪Let's be friends.
‪-Did get tear up?
‪-His nose kind of…
‪Let's be friends.
‪Kang Kyung-ho did not return
‪Lee Ye-rim's feelings.
‪Please put your glass jar
‪back in its original place
‪and return to your position.
‪Our timing was a bit off
‪and some other things didn't line up.
‪I'm a bit disappointed about that.
‪But to be honest,
‪when all that stuff first went down,
‪I was a bit resentful
‪and obviously a little jealous.
‪I got angry when I felt
‪like I wasn't being respected,
‪but I know not everything can go
‪the way I want.
‪I realize now that I need
‪to respect his choices.
‪I was able to understand better
‪the more we talked.
‪And I think I learned how
‪to speak more gently
‪and initiate conversation.
‪I'm thankful that he heard me out.
‪I think he's a remarkable guy too.
‪I wanted to tell him that.
‪-She's bound to meet a better person.
‪-For sure.
‪Park Ga-yeon.
‪Bring your Heart Chips
‪and stand in front of the table.
‪If you want to confess
‪your feelings to Park Ga-yeon,
‪bring your Heart Chips
‪and stand in front of the table.
‪When you gain something,
‪you lose something too.
‪I have mixed feelings.
‪I used all my Heart Chips on Ga-yeon.
‪KANG KYUNG-HO COMPLETED VOTING
‪ALL CHIPS → PARK GA-YEON
‪She made me feel things
‪I never expected to feel.
‪I think that's why I chose her in the end.
‪KYUNG-HO → GA-YEON
‪FINAL CHOICE
‪JUNG-MIN → GA-YEON
‪A lot changed yesterday,
‪and I wish we had more time
‪and things worked out differently.
‪But my feelings didn't change much.
‪YOU MADE THIS EXPERIENCE MORE FUN FOR ME
‪BY MAKING ME FEEL AND THINK MANY THINGS
‪EVEN THOUGH IT TURNED OUT THIS WAY,
‪THANKS FOR THE LAST FIVE DAYS
‪She's the person I spoke to the most
‪and the person I was most attracted to.
‪She was the prettiest in my eyes.
‪JUNG-MIN USED
‪ALL HIS HEART CHIPS LAST NIGHT
‪Ga-yeon.
‪First of all, thanks for spending
‪most of the last five days with me.
‪She was the most fun
‪and comfortable to be around.
‪Will you go on a date with me tomorrow?
‪Yes.
‪It's because of Ga-yeon
‪that I was able to feel this way.
‪She gave me something
‪to look forward to.
‪Seven, six…
‪The talks we had
‪and the things we did together
‪on our dates were so much fun.
‪Five days is huge.
‪It's not like they went home
‪at the end of the day.
‪-They were constantly together.
‪-Five days the whole time.
‪Those two were basically inseparable
‪and even physical.
‪I'd like to keep spending
‪most of my time with you,
‪and I'll keep rooting for you.
‪The more time passed,
‪I was able to see many sides of Ga-yeon.
‪I know you really like to win,
‪so I appreciated it
‪when you said you lost to me.
‪I was glad to share
‪this experience with you.
‪Let's leave this place together.
‪I felt a lot of emotions
‪that I'd forgotten how to feel.
‪Like feeling excited
‪or jealous.
‪Because of her and the situation
‪being out of my control,
‪the feeling of my head about to burst…
‪It brought up emotions I'd forgotten.
‪I think that will really stay with me.
‪Park Ga-yeon, please give your answer
‪to each person's confession
‪and pour all the Heart Chips
‪of the person you choose
‪into your glass jar.
‪PARK GA-YEON USED
‪ALL HER HEART CHIPS LAST NIGHT
‪Jung-min.
‪You're a really caring
‪and attentive person.
‪I will
‪keep rooting for you too.
‪Kyung-ho. You made
‪my heart race
‪and made me excited.
‪Let's take things calmly
‪and see each other for a long time.
‪GA-YEON → KYUNG-HO
‪FINAL CHOICE
‪Park Ga-yeon did not return
‪Park Jung-min's feelings.
‪Please put your glass jar
‪back in its original place
‪and return to your position.
‪For me, the final choice means
‪choosing someone I could consider
‪having a serious relationship with.
‪That was Ga-yeon.
‪It felt like I missed out
‪on something that's even rarer,
‪so it's that much more
‪sad and disappointing.
‪I feel like crying right now, honestly.
‪But I'll be okay when I get home.
‪Time heals all wounds.
‪I think Jung-min gave his all.
‪Of course,
‪I'd like to stay really good friends
‪once we get out.
‪But that might be asking for too much.
‪So however he feels
‪and whatever he decides to do,
‪I just have to accept it.
‪Kyung-ho confessed his feelings
‪and held hands with her too,
‪but they're not officially dating.
‪So who knows what could happen?
‪I took a ton of selfies with her
‪in matching outfits.
‪I won't delete them
‪even if she dates Kyung-ho.
‪Congratulations.
‪You are the third couple
‪of the first King of Hearts game.
‪PARK GA-YEON, KANG KYUNG-HO
‪He's a charming guy.
‪He completely shattered
‪my idea of what I was looking for.
‪It wasn't a matter of what my ideals were.
‪Kyung-ho was the person I felt drawn to.
‪And I know for sure I want to date him.
‪GA-YEON'S MESSAGE TO KYUNG-HO LAST NIGHT
‪Let's take things calmly
‪and see other for a long time.
‪Let's meet up often
‪even after we get out.
‪KYUNG-HO WROTE A SIMILAR MESSAGE
‪I plan to see her for a long time,
‪but I want her to know
‪I have no intention of keeping it calm.
‪I hope we'll feel this way
‪and stay this way for a long time.
‪KYUNG-HO AND GA-YEON
‪FINAL COUPLE
‪The first King of Hearts game has ended.
‪It's been a long road. Goodness.
‪Seriously.
‪Three couples. That's impressive.
‪There were three successful couples.
‪It could have been four couples
‪if not for that final twist at the end.
‪That's really impressive.
‪At first, the concept of a king
‪seemed kind of silly,
‪and I wondered if we even needed it.
‪But the king became
‪increasingly important.
‪The people who weren't king
‪became more dependent on the king.
‪So the king's choices
‪and one's relationship with the king
‪became really important.
‪It was a really weird
‪dating show in that way.
‪When you wanted to go
‪on a date with someone,
‪you had to go to the king and say,
‪"I want to date this person,"
‪so it made me a lot more proactive.
‪And it made me more aware of my feelings.
‪Make me king.
‪Either me or Ga-yeon
‪will become king today.
‪We have to keep her in check.
‪For the sake of love,
‪I came up with strategies
‪and plotted and schemed.
‪Have I always been the kind of person
‪who goes this far for love?
‪We can use underhanded tactics.
‪The only tactic I can use now
‪is making you king.
‪The king played a huge role
‪in every aspect.
‪You had to be good to the king
‪to get what you wanted.
‪That's how the game worked.
‪Whoever you tried to keep in check
‪was a pretty clear indicator
‪of who they wanted to date.
‪It was so much fun.
‪You could indirectly find out
‪what the other person was feeling,
‪so that was nice.
‪The King of Hearts Game
‪gave us a lot of chances.
‪On top of love,
‪there was more fun involved.
‪AND NOW
‪"And now…"
‪Here we go.
‪Will we see results?
‪-Of course, we will!
‪-We have to!
‪DO-GEON AND CHAE-RIN
‪MET IN HYEHWA THE VERY NEXT DAY
‪THEY WENT ON A BOWLING DATE AS PROMISED
‪GA-YEON & KYUNG-HO, HYE-WON & HA-YOON
‪WENT ON A DOUBLE DATE
‪They even went on a double date!
‪UNBOXING WHAT THEY MADE
‪DURING THE POTTERY DATE
‪Thanks.
‪-I'll use this well.
‪-Okay.
‪Bon app‪é‪tit.
‪A DAY OUT BY THE HANGANG RIVER
‪I prefer the 7 to the SE.
‪The color?
‪DRAWING TOGETHER
‪CUSTOM COUPLE CAPS
‪COUPLE CAP SELFIES
‪Like that, the King of Heart game
‪is over.
‪More importantly,
‪it's the end of The Love Lab.
‪That's right.
‪-It's a shame.
‪-What did you think of it?
‪It was so much fun.
‪-It was.
‪-Seriously, I just had fun watching.
‪Same.
‪The participants were all so sincere
‪and it was so much fun.
‪I would like to thank everyone.
‪We're sorry if you got hurt
‪by any of our reactions.
‪We were just being dramatic
‪to make some money.
‪If we can do so,
‪let's go for a meal together…
‪Come to our wrap-up dinner!
‪Come and tell us what was hard
‪and what was frustrating,
‪Ye-rim!
‪Let's all get together…
‪-And talk it all out.
‪-Yes, let's talk it all out!
‪-Yes.
‪-Yeah.
‪-Thank you.
‪Subtitle translation by: Hannah Og Nam
‪THE LOVE LAB